I cut to it so the transition is not completely straight.
I want some turn on it.
Then I have had to weld and put in pieces to get a good fit.
-The whole door have you built up and knocked yourself?
Yes.
-You are good.
Well...
...stubborn.
On the inside I have tried to rose polish.
The same way as the dashboard but it was difficult.
I can't do it in the pillar drill because it gets too deep.
So I tried by hand but it should be dressed with leather instead.
With a compartment here in leather.
Was how you wanted to do?
Yes, it is difficult with rose polishing.
It is a hot thing if you have a computer that presses just as hard and has the same type of grinding.
Then you get smooth and nice results.
-How long did it take to make the door?
Yes how long did it take ....
Hmmm ...
You put it first here ...
Now it should be below this so it should be put there first.
Then you attach the mirror so.
What is missing now is the passenger door.
And fit the rest.
I smooth out the body with armored file.
-Pansar file?
Body file says many experts.
It is used to get a smooth surface.
To get rid of small elevations that exist.
And after that I start grinding with sandpaper.
Should I grind with sandpaper now, it just follows the bumps.
The armored file removes the bumps so you can grind then.
-How much planes it huh?
You have to stand for a long time.
You have to be careful so you do not get oblique.
Then you cut a jack into the plate.
Then you have to plan the entire area so that the jacket disappears.
You can't just plan in the same place.
Then there will be a pit there when polishing.
If you have a pit or a jack, you have to plan everything down until you get to the same level.
This surface takes about 5 hours to plan.
Here it is smoother and then it takes 2-3 hours with armored file.
There are various grinders you can use.
I tried a machine that lacquers call pancake.
It is a little bigger and has oscillating grinding.
It makes this movement.
And it also forced rotates.
An ordinary Oscillery grinding machine does not spin it just vibrates.
This machine spins and makes an oscillating motion.
Then it is easy to get the surface smooth.
I have tried that machine on this page and therefore it became much smoother.
That is why I should do the other side.
And then this type of abrasive paper is used.
This abrasive paper is larger than ordinary.
So it takes a larger area and it is easier to get flat.
-What do you start with for abrasive paper?
This is 180.
Then it becomes this surface.
I use window cleaning.
I think that is smoother.
It gets a little halter and does not chop as much and easier to wipe.
-This is crafts without its like.
Yes it is ... we can take the other instead.
This one is stuck.
It is instead of chrome or painting.
It has a tendency to be burned fairly quickly.
So it's better to make a cover covering over.
-Mm, such a cover you do in 20 min ... NO half an hour..hahaha!
-Crazy!
No it takes a little longer.
Here you get some cooling.
Yes.
It takes in the air here and releases it on the underside.
I thought it looked a little naked so I turned sleeves.
So it looks like it is a screw and there is a little more life in it.
The screws will be replaced so there will be recessed screws with lids in brass.
Here will be brass washers.
-You have an eye for details.
That's the fun.
That is the icing on the cake.
-It's what makes the difference.
I think it can be good ... you can always hope.
-Here you have started sketching the rims.
Yes.
I want a different piece on them than original.
That is an original rim.
Spinnersen I do not want so I have also shortened this cover and made it tighter.